# Shakhboz Uktamov

Full Stack Developer

## **Profile**

Web developer or engineer with 5 years of experience who works with both the front and back ends of a website or application.

Provide an end-to-end service, and can be involved in projects that involve databases and building user-facing websites.

#### **Contact**

- 9
- +1-718-715-8960
- M
- shaxbozuktamov4@gmail.com
- **(**
- www.shakhboz.com
- 0
- Brooklyn, New York 11214

## Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Node
- React
- React Native
- DevOps
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- AWS
- REST API
- Linux
- GitHub

## **Education**

(2021-2022)

**TECH MAKTAB LLC** 

Full Stack Web Development

(2012-2015)

**COMMUNITY COLLEGE** 

Accounting

## **Experience**

(2022-2023)

#### **TECH MAKTAB LLC**

Full Stack Developer

- Design and Develop Restful APIs
- Understood full technology stack and underlying applications, services and databases, resulting in optimal program performance.
- Managed front-end and back-end development in the company's Employee Track, and Account Management systems.

(2018-2022)

#### **DAGINOZ INC**

Front-End Web Developer

- Database administration and website design
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled
- Educational institutions and online classroom management
- Designed and implemented scalable application programming interfaces.
- Adopted engineering best practices and delivered highest quality scalable solutions.